#### Contact

No.12,3D Apt, Marlar 3rd Street, Mayangone Township Yangon, 06, 11062

09894396852

sulapyae2017@gmail.co

### Skills

Japanese

Very Good

English

Very Good

Thai

Good

Office Excel

Average

Graphic design

Good

Business administration

Good

Digital illustration



# Su La Pyae

# Japanese Teacher

My name is Su La Pyae. I had graduated from YUFL with English major. I am at the English upper Intermediate level . And I have passed N2 in JLPT which is held countrywide. My most experience are working as Japanese Teacher specializing in Japanese grammar based on Minna no Nihongo text book. Competent college-level teacher bringing proven success as Japanese teacher over successful career. Effectively interest students in subject matter to drive home information and broaden horizons. Polished speaker and presenter with excellent record keeping and tutoring skills.

### Work History

# 2019-09 - Japanese Language Teacher

JPL, Yangon, KyeeMyintDing

My main function is instructing japanese N5 and N4 level to the students

- Coordinated special excursions to local points of interests and more extensive study trips to expand learning for Japanese -language students.
- Delivered 30 hours per week of classroom lectures, instructing over 40 students per semester in language.
- Facilitated positive learning environment by using enthusiastic and energetic instructional strategies and consistent classroom management.
- Developed team communications and information for instructor meetings.
- Monitored social media and online sources for industry trends.
- Immersed students in unfamiliar cultures by devising hands-on activities.
- Organized detailed list of resources to help students go beyond classroom environments and delve into topics of interest.

### 2019-01 - Home Japanese Teacher

Home, Yangon, Southokkalapa, Kamaryut

 Increased customer satisfaction by resolving language difficulty issues.

#### 2018-01 - English Teacher 2018-07 Supertop Academy.

Supertop Academy, Yangon, Kamaryut my role in there is teaching the students four skills especially in grammar and speaking.

- Prepared comprehensive English curriculum for five students.
- Built learning and citizenship skills to help with personal growth in addition to increasing academic knowledge.

# Education

2019-06

2016-01 - Bachelor of Arts: English Language And 2019-09 Literature

Yangon University Of Foerign Languages - Kamaryut

- Professional development completed in English literature and Business English.
- Minored in Political Science, language analysis.

2017-12 - Japanese

2018-03 Japanese Language Proficiency Test (N3) -

Botahtoung

2018-12 - **Japanese** 2019-05 - Japanese La

Japanese Language Proficiency Test (N2) -

Kamaryut